[upbeat rock music]
- Hey, guys.
- 嘿，伙计们。
We've got some pretty exciting news.
我们有一些非常令人兴奋的消息。
We want you to meet the foreign exchange student
我们想让你们见见来自澳大利亚的交换生
from Australia who just moved in with us.
他刚刚搬来和我们一起住。
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嘿。 - 嘿。
- G'day. Nice to meet you all.
- 你好。很高兴见到你们。
I'm Britt.
我是布里特。
- You talk funny.
- 你说话真奇怪。
- What did you say?
- 你说什么？
- You'll get used to it.
你会习惯的。
I'm Mae. - And I'm Miles.
我是Mae。
- I'm Dooley. - I'm very excited to be here.
我是Miles。
It's gonna be ripper.
我是Dooley。
- Absolutely. Totally ripper.
我非常兴奋能来到这里。
What's ripper?
这将会非常棒。
- It means really great.
绝对是的。完全棒极了。
As in, "Since I'm an only child,
什么是'ripper'？
it's gonna be ripper to finally have a sister and brothers."
它的意思是非常好。
[together] Ripper.
比如说，'因为我是独生子女，终于有了姐姐和兄弟，这将会非常棒。'
- Yeah, by the way, where's Dicky?
是的，顺便问一下，Dicky在哪儿？
- Oh he's probably still watching the toilet flush.
哦，他可能还在看马桶冲水。
- Ew.
呃。
- Oh, no, it's not what you think.
哦，不，不是你想的那样。
Ever since Britt told him Australian toilets
自从Britt告诉他澳大利亚的马桶
flush the opposite way, Dicky's been in the bathroom
冲水方向相反后，Dicky就一直待在浴室里
trying to make the water spin backwards.
试图让水反向旋转。
- That makes sense. - Yeah, that sounds right.
那说得通。
- Still ew.
是的，听起来没错。
- Do a lot of Americans talk like that?
还是觉得恶心。
- [whispering] No.
不。
- Come on, Britt, let us introduce you to
来吧，Britt，让我们带你了解一下
some typical American sports and hobbies.
一些典型的美国运动和爱好。
- Ooh, check these out.
哦，看看这些。
- Is it okay to just open those like that?
这样直接打开可以吗？
- [scoffs] Our parents own the store.
（轻蔑地）我们的父母拥有这家店。
- We can do whatever we want.
我们可以想做什么就做什么。
- Our lives are just that ripper.
我们的生活就是那么自由。
- Oh, this is not gonna end well.
哦，这不会有什么好结果的。
- Okay. Britt, these are golf balls.
好的。Britt，这些是高尔夫球。
- Yeah, we have the Australian Open.
是的，我们有澳大利亚公开赛。
- Those are tennis balls.
那些是网球。
- There's an Australian Open for tennis too.
网球也有澳大利亚公开赛。
- Well, I bet there's no open for...
好吧，我打赌没有...
miniature hockey.
迷你曲棍球的比赛。
- That's a boomerang.
那是个回旋镖。
And there's a cup, not an open.
而且是个杯赛，不是公开赛。
- I knew that, Britt.
我知道的，布里特。
It's American humor.
这是美式幽默。
- I bet you use those a lot back home.
我打赌你在老家经常用这些。
- Not really. It's just in the movies.
- 并不常。只是在电影里见过。
- Oh, so you don't know how to use it?
- 哦，这么说你不会用？
- Of course I know how to use it.
- 当然会用。
I'm Australian. Don't you watch movies?
我是澳大利亚人。你们不看电影吗？
- Well, can you show us how to throw it?
- 那你能教我们怎么扔吗？
- Absolutely. But it's best to do it outside.
- 当然可以。但最好在外面扔。
- Again, Britt-- parents own the store.
- 再说一次，Britt——这家店是父母开的。
- Yeah, so go ahead.
- 对，那就开始吧。
You can boom your rang in here.
你可以在这里扔回旋镖。
- I wouldn't say it like that in Australia,
- 在澳大利亚我不会这么说，
but here we go.
但这里我们开始了。
[boomerang whooshing]
[回旋镖呼啸声]
[all exclaiming]
[众人惊呼]
- I got to try that.
- 我得试试这个。
both: Me too.
两人: 我也是。
- Oh, this is definitely not gonna end well.
- 哦，这肯定不会有好结果。
- Here we go.
- 开始了。
[crashing]
[撞击声]
- Crikey!
- 哎呀！
- Don't worry, Britt. This isn't a "crikey."
- 别担心，Britt。这不是一个“哎呀”的情况。
- Crikey or no crikey,
- 不管是不是'crikey'，
you guys really boomed that rang.
你们真的把那铃声搞得震天响。
- I don't think you're saying it right.
- 我觉得你说的不对。
- Nobody is saying any of it right.
- 没人说得对。
- [gasps] - Kids?
- [惊呼] - 孩子们？
- What did you do?
- 你们做了什么？
You know we have the special release of Isaiah Thomas'
你知道我们明天有以赛亚·托马斯的新款以赛亚T-4运动鞋的特别发售。
new Isaiah T-4 sneakers tomorrow.
- 是的。 - 我们很兴奋。
- Yeah. - We're psyched.
- 我迫不及待要把脚
- I can't wait to put my feet
伸进那些鞋里。
in those babies.
把我的脚放进那些宝贝里。
- Then why would you trash the store?
那你为什么要弄脏店铺？
We just found out that Isaiah Thomas himself
我们刚得知以赛亚·托马斯本人
is gonna be here signing shoes.
会来这里给鞋子签名。
[all exclaiming]
[众人惊呼]
- And since the promotional price is only $4 a pair,
而且因为促销价每双只要4美元,
there's gonna be a ton of people here to see...
会有很多人来这里看...
this!
这个！
- Okay, you know what?
好吧，你知道吗？
We are so tired of you guys
我们真是受够了你们这些人在这里
acting so entitled around here,
在这里表现得如此理所当然，
so if you want Isaiah T-4s,
所以如果你想买Isaiah T-4s，
you are gonna have to wait in line outside
你就得像其他人一样在外面排队等候
and pay for them like everyone else.
并且像其他人一样付款。
- Told you it wasn't gonna end well.
我告诉过你这不会有什么好结果。
- And you better plan on getting up early,
而且你最好计划早起，
because there's only 104 pair of those 4s.
因为只有104双那种4s。
- Did you say, "Wait in line"?
你是说，“排队等候”？
- "Outside"? - "Like everyone else"?
“在外面”？ - “像其他人一样”？
What do you mean?
你是什么意思？
- I think she means you guys are gonna have to wait in line,
- 我想她的意思是你們得像其他人一樣排隊等著，
outside, like everyone else.
在外面。
- Thanks, Britt, but we've got this.
- 謝了，布里特，但我們搞得定。
See, there's no language barrier between us
你看，我們和父母之間沒有語言障礙，
and our parents, and they would never expect us
他們絕不會想到我們需要排隊。
to wait in line.
- 實際上，那正是我們所期望的。
- Actually, that's exactly what we expect.
[一起] 天哪。
[together] Crikey.
[輕快的音樂]
[upbeat music]
- ♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[口哨聲]
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[cheerful music]
- I can't believe Mom and Dad
- 我真不敢相信爸妈
made us clean up the entire store
- 让我们打扫整个店
and are still gonna make us wait in line.
- 还要我们排队等着。
Like a bunch of liner-uppers.
- 像一群排队的人。
- Well, I'm excited.
- 不过，我挺兴奋的。
My first American experience
我的第一次美国体验
meeting an American sports star,
遇见一位美国体育明星，
buying American sneakers,
购买美国运动鞋，
and standing in an American line.
以及站在美国的队伍中。
- You know, you really don't need
你知道，你真的不需要
to specify everything as American.
把每件事都特别强调是美国式的。
- Gotcha, mate!
明白了，伙计！
- Also, you don't have to be so upbeat about everything.
而且，你不必对每件事都这么乐观。
It's kind of watering down our outrage.
这有点削弱了我们的愤怒情绪。
- Gotcha, mate!
明白了，伙计！
I mean...
我是说...
[quietly] Gotcha, mate.
[轻声]明白了，伙计。
You may resume your outrage.
你可以继续表达你的愤怒了。
- Thank you.
谢谢。
As I was saying, we're not liner-uppers.
正如我所说，我们不是排队的人。
We're plan-hatchers.
我们是策划者。
- Ooh! Here's a plan for ya! all: Yeah?
哦！这里有个计划给你！
- We go to bed early... all: Yeah?
我们早点上床...
- We wake up early... all: Yeah?
我们早点起床...
- And we wait in line. all: No!
然后我们排队等候。
- Britt, Britt, Britt,
布里特，布里特，布里特，
leave the hatching to me.
孵化计划交给我吧。
Planning's kind of my thing.
规划可是我的强项。
- You didn't hear the best part.
你还没听到最精彩的部分呢。
When we wake up early, I'll make you some eggs.
我们早起的时候，我会给你做些鸡蛋。
How do you like 'em? - [chuckles]
你喜欢怎么吃？
Britt, Britt, Britt,
布里特，布里特，布里特，
leave the breakfast to me.
早餐也交给我吧。
Cooking's kind of my thing.
烹饪也是我的拿手好戏。
- Since we're carving out our areas of expertise here,
既然我们都在划分各自的专业领域，
sweater vests, bedazzling, math--all me.
毛衣背心，装饰，数学——全是我。
- No judgment, mate.
- 不评判，伙计。
What's Dicky's area of expertise?
Dicky的专长是什么？
[toilet flushing]
[厕所冲水声]
Oh, right.
哦，对了。
- Okay, we need a plan
- 好吧，我们需要一个计划
to get us out of waiting in line
让我们不用排队
like a bunch of dummies.
像一群傻瓜一样。
That's it! Plan hatched!
就是这样！计划已定！
both: Nice.
两人: 不错。
- Is she gonna explain more, or...?
她会解释更多吗，还是...？
- Nope. Just nod and go with it.
不，只要点头跟着做就行了。
- Then we'll question it when we get there.
那我们到了那里再问。
Okay, a couple questions.
好的，有几个问题。
First, are you sure this is gonna work?
首先，你确定这会有效吗？
- Yep.
是的。
- Actually, that was our only question.
实际上，那是我们唯一的问题。
- Okay, mission accomplished.
好的，任务完成了。
Now we can sleep in
现在我们可以睡个好觉了
while these dummies hold our spots
而这些傻瓜会帮我们占着位置
at the front of the line.
在队伍的最前面。
Where are our dummies?
我们的替身在哪里？
- Guess somebody thought our mannequin plan was garbage.
我猜有人认为我们的假人计划是垃圾。
- Why would you say that?
你为什么这么说？
- Because our mannequins are in the garbage.
因为我们的假人现在在垃圾桶里。
- Okay, new plan. There's Mae and Miles.
好吧，新计划。那里有Mae和Miles。
They'll let us cut in front of them.
他们会让我们插队到他们前面。
Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
- G'day.
早上好。
- Listen, we kind of overslept this morning--
听着，我们今天早上有点睡过头了——
- You mean you used mannequins to hold your spot
- 你的意思是用假人占位
at the front of the line?
在队伍的最前面？
- I suppose that's possible.
- 我想是有可能的。
- And people got mad, tore 'em apart,
- 然后人们生气了，把它们撕碎，
and threw 'em into the dumpster?
扔进了垃圾桶？
- Also possible.
- 也有可能。
- There's a dumpster full of mannequins right over there.
- 那边就有一个装满假人的垃圾桶。
- Well, you can't prove we had anything to do with it.
- 好吧，你不能证明我们与此有关。
- They have nametags.
- 它们身上有名牌。
- Are you gonna let us cut or not?
- 你们到底让不让我们插队？
- Please? It's just a little cut-sies.
- 请？只是小小的切割而已。
- No.
- 不行。
And don't try to make it sound cute.
别试图把它说得那么可爱。
- But it's just a little cut-sies.
- 但真的只是小小的切割。
- All right, fine.
- 好吧，好吧。
- Miles! - What?
- 迈尔斯！ - 什么？
It's just so charming when he says it.
他这么说的时候真是迷人。
[whistle blows]
[哨声响起]
- No cut-sies!
- 不许切割！
all: Dooley?
大家：杜利？
- What are you doing?
- 你在干什么？
- Your parents said they'd give me a free pair
- 你父母说如果我保持队伍秩序，他们会给我一双签名的以赛亚鞋。
of signed Isaiah shoes if I kept the line in order.
- 等等，所以他们惩罚了我们
- Wait, so they punished us
- 然后雇你来监督队伍？
and then hired you to watch the line?
- 不，只是监督你们。
- No, just to watch you.
- 所以不能插队？
- So no cut-sies?
- 好吧。但只针对你。
- All right. But just you.
- 所有人: 杜利！ - 对！
all: Dooley! - Right!
- 回到队伍后面去，你们所有人。
Back of the line, all of you.
- 对不起。
Sorry.
对不起。
- No worries.
别担心。
That means we get to spend more time together.
这意味着我们可以多花点时间在一起。
Come on, Harpers. Let's hop on over there.
快点，哈珀家的人。我们过去那边吧。
- Look, I love that Britt
看，我喜欢布里特
never gets outraged by anything,
从不因任何事感到愤怒，
but his lack of outrage is outraging me.
但他缺乏愤怒让我感到愤怒。
- This is not shaping up to be such a g'day.
看来今天不会是个好日子。
- Come on, Harpers.
快点，哈珀家的人。
[all sighing]
（大家都叹气）
♪ ♪
[cheerful music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Was the line this long for the first three versions
- 前三个版本的以赛亚鞋排队也这么长吗？
of Isaiah's shoes?
- 我们不知道。
- We don't know.
我们不需要排队。
We didn't have to wait in line.
- 我曾在Woolloomooloo为了买一块虎皮派等了三个小时。
- I once waited three hours
那真是太棒了。
for a tiger pie in Woolloomooloo.
- 嘿，'太棒了'的反义词是什么？
It was ripper.
因为这就是那个。
- Hey, what's the opposite of ripper?
嘿，ripper的反义词是什么？
Because this is that.
因为这就是那个反义词。
- This one's as feisty as a boxing kangaroo.
这个就像拳击袋鼠一样火爆。
- I should be insulted by that, but I'm charmed.
我本该觉得被冒犯了，但我被迷住了。
- That accent lets you get away with anything.
那个口音让你可以为所欲为。
- Teach us how to get away with anything.
教我们如何为所欲为。
- All right, let's give it a burl.
好吧，让我们试试看。
Here's an easy one.
这里有个简单的。
Down under, we shave with "rye-zuh blides."
在澳洲，我们用“rye-zuh blides”刮胡子。
Repeat after me: "rye-zuh blides."
跟我重复：“rye-zuh blides”。
all: Razor blades.
大家一起说：剃须刀片。
- No, say "rye."
不对，要说“rye”。
all: Rye.
大家一起说：Rye。
- Zuh. all: Zuh.
大家一起说：Zuh。
- Blides. all: Blides.
大家一起说：Blides。
- Now all together.
现在大家一起说。
all: Razor blades.
大家一起说：剃须刀片。
- Okay, we've got some work to do.
好吧，我们还有些工作要做。
- Hey, Dooley! Those people just cut.
嘿，杜利！那些人刚刚切了。
What's that all about? - No idea.
这是怎么回事？不知道。
Not here to watch them, just you.
不是来看他们的，只是看你。
And you're terrible at accents.
而且你的口音很糟糕。
- You can't give us a ticket for being bad at accents.
你不能因为我们口音不好就给我们开罚单。
- Can. Did.
可以。已经开了。
Rye-zuh blides, rye-zuh blides...
锐-扎布莱兹，锐-扎布莱兹...
- Great. We just got bumped out of sneaker range.
太好了。我们刚被踢出了运动鞋范围。
- And we have a court date in three weeks.
而且我们三周后还有法庭日期。
- One problem at a time.
一次解决一个问题。
Those people are out of line.
那些人太过分了。
We need to get them out of line!
我们需要让他们回到正轨！
- Look at the kangaroo go!
看那袋鼠跳！
- But how are we gonna get them out of line
但我们怎么让他们不越界呢？
when all they want to see is Isaiah?
当他们只想见以赛亚时？
- Now I have a plan!
现在我有个计划！
- I thought she was the plan-hatcher
我以为她才是计划制定者
and you were the cook.
而你是执行者。
- Well, I cooked up a plan, okay?
好吧，我想出了一个计划，行了吧？
And you're coming with me, bloomin' onion.
而且你要跟我一起去，洋葱头。
- Where's Nicky?
尼基在哪儿？
- You'll see. [laughs]
你会看到的。[笑]
Hey, look, everybody!
It's NBA superstar Isaiah Thomas!
- [deep voice] Oh, no. I've been spotted.
Back down the alley I go.
- Yes! - Nice!
- Looks like we're back in shoe-gettin' range.
- We did it! We've won! - Hold on.
This is the part where it looks like we've won,
but if we're not careful,
we'll get distracted by something.
So stay focused.
所以保持专注。
- Hot tots!
- 热乎的薯球！
all: Ooh.
大家：哦。
- [laughing] - Hey, Gladys.
- [笑着说] - 嘿，格拉迪斯。
You sell street tots?
你卖街边薯球吗？
- Summer's slow for us lunch ladies.
- 对我们这些食堂阿姨来说，夏天生意比较淡。
I make a few bucks slinging tots on the side.
我顺便卖点薯球赚点外快。
- Gladys, we have an Australian exchange student.
- 格拉迪斯，我们有个澳大利亚交换生。
- What does that have to do with tots?
- 这跟薯球有什么关系？
- Did you know that in Australia
- 你知道在澳大利亚
we call tater tots potato gems?
我们称tater tots为potato gems？
- Oh, you don't say.
- 哦，真的吗？
Hot gems! Get your hot potato gems!
热gems！来买热potato gems！
Nah, don't like it.
不，不喜欢。
Even though you're cute as a koala.
尽管你像考拉一样可爱。
- Fair enough.
- 说得通。
We'll take four orders of hot tots.
我们要四份热tots。
- That'll be $16.
- 那将是16美元。
- $16?
- 16美元？
- They're organic.
- 它们是有机的。
- Hey, kids,
嘿，孩子们，
Isaiah Thomas just arrived,
以赛亚·托马斯刚到，
so we'll be opening the doors shortly.
所以我们很快就会开门。
- Oh, I hope you have enough money
哦，希望你有足够的钱
for tots and shoes.
买薯球和鞋子。
- We barely had tot money.
我们几乎只有买薯球的钱。
- Yeah, we thought our lesson was having to wait in line
是啊，我们以为我们的教训是要排队
like everybody else.
像其他人一样。
- We also said you had to buy them.
我们还说过你得自己买。
- Yeah, but with your money, not ours.
是啊，但用你的钱，不是我们的。
- Sorry, kids. No special treatment.
对不起，孩子们。没有特殊待遇。
- Hey, you were right.
嘿，你说对了。
It did look like we were gonna win,
看起来我们真的要赢了，
and then we got distracted by the lovely lady
然后我们被那位迷人的女士
and her hot tots.
和她美味的炸薯条分心了。
- We can still fix this.
我们还能解决这个问题。
I'll just go home and get our money.
我回家拿我们的钱。
So tell me where you guys keep yours.
所以告诉我你们的钱放在哪儿。
- How about no.
还是算了吧。
- Fine. We'll all go together.
好吧。我们一起去。
Britt, save our spots.
布里特，帮我们占住位置。
- Shh!
嘘！
Here you go, Hugh Jackman.
给你，休·杰克曼。
Don't tell anybody.
别告诉任何人。
Hot tots!
热辣小点心！
♪ ♪
- Come on, guys!
快点，伙计们！
We have to get back to the store!
我们得回店里去！
Oh, interesting.
哦，有意思。
Your secret cash stash is in the kitchen.
你的秘密现金藏匿处在厨房。
Bet I can guess where.
我敢打赌我能猜到在哪里。
- No way. - Tea kettle.
不可能。- 茶壶。
- Shoot!
该死！
Then I'll just use my other secret hiding place.
那我就用我的另一个秘密藏匿处。
- Bread box. - Shoot!
面包盒。 - 该死！
Then I'll just use my other secret--
那我就用我的另一个秘密——
- Sugar bowl. - You're a witch.
糖碗。 - 你是个巫师。
- Guys, we have a problem.
伙计们，我们有麻烦了。
Dicky's not upstairs,
迪基不在楼上，
and all his clothes are missing.
而且他所有的衣服都不见了。
And I found this.
然后我找到了这个。
- So? We all know he loves popping bubble wrap.
所以呢？我们都知道他喜欢捏泡泡纸。
- Or he boxed himself up
或者他自己把自己装进了箱子
and mailed himself to Australia!
然后把自己寄到澳大利亚去了！
- What? - Why would you think that?
什么？
- I was so tired of him talking about
你为什么会这么想？
how Australian toilets flush the opposite way,
我实在是听腻了他谈论
I may have maybe kind of suggested
澳大利亚的马桶冲水方向是反的，
that he box himself up and mail himself
我可能也许有点暗示他
to Australia to find out.
把自己装进箱子然后寄到澳大利亚去验证一下。
- That's ridiculous. How is that even possible?
- 这太荒谬了。怎么可能做到呢？
- I'll tell you how.
- 我来告诉你怎么做到。
That's how.
就是这样。
- Even if he could box himself up,
- 即使他能把自己装进箱子，
someone would still have to give it to a delivery person.
还是需要有人把它交给快递员。
Who would do that? - I'll tell you who.
谁会这么做？ - 我来告诉你谁会。
- Here for a pickup? - Oh, this must be it.
- 来取件的吗？ - 哦，肯定是这个了。
My wife's probably returning a bunch of shoes.
我老婆可能退了一大堆鞋子。
- [grunts]
- [咕哝声]
Wow, this sure is heavy for shoes.
哇，这鞋子可真重。
- Yeah, well, she has really big feet.
- 是啊，她脚真的很大。
- Okay.
- 好吧。
- Here, well--I'm sorry. Here, let me help.
- 来，嗯——对不起。来，让我帮忙。
Just--hold this. - Uh-huh.
就——拿着这个。 - 嗯哼。
- So you want to bend your legs like this.
- 所以你要这样弯曲你的腿。
- That's who.
- 就是那个人。
- Listen, I'm sure Dicky is just pranking us.
- 听着，我肯定迪基只是在跟我们开玩笑。
But right now, we have to get back to the line
但现在，我们得回到队伍中去
so we can get our Isaiah T-4s.
这样我们才能拿到我们的以赛亚T-4。
By the way, you may want to move your secret stash.
顺便说一句，你可能想移动你的秘密藏匿处。
I have a feeling it's in your sock drawer.
我有种感觉它在你袜子抽屉里。
- No, it's not. - Far right,
- 不，不在那里。 - 在最右边，
inside the bedazzled tie box.
在那个镶钻的领带盒里。
- Witch.
- 女巫。
♪ ♪
- Great! You've got your money.
- 太好了！你拿到钱了。
You're back in line.
你回到队伍里了。
Nothing can stop us now.
现在没有什么能阻止我们了。
[whistle blows] - Line violation. No cut-sies.
[哨声响起] - 违规插队。不许插队。
- Come on, Dooley. We're not cutting.
- 拜托，杜利。我们没有插队。
- Yeah. Britt was just saving our spot for us.
是啊，布里特只是帮我们占了个位置。
- Then no save-sies. Back of the line.
那就不许占位。回到队尾去。
- Charm him, Britt.
去说服他，布里特。
- I really like your--
我真的很喜欢你的——
- ♪ Ah la la la la la ♪
♪啊啦啦啦啦啦♪
Back of the line!
回到队尾！
♪ La la la la la la ♪
♪啦啦啦啦啦啦♪
♪ ♪
♪♪
- Great. Now we're definitely out of sneaker range.
太好了。现在我们肯定买不起运动鞋了。
- Wow, once again, victory was within our grasp.
哇，又一次，胜利近在咫尺。
But then, another wallop.
但接着，又是一记重击。
Well, at least things can't get any worse.
好吧，至少事情不能再糟糕了。
- They just did.
- 它们刚刚变得更糟了。
I was calling Dicky earlier,
我之前给迪基打电话，
but he didn't answer,
但他没接，
so I've been trying to track his phone,
所以我一直在尝试追踪他的手机，
and I finally found him.
我终于找到他了。
- So where is he?
- 那他在哪儿？
- Halfway across the Pacific Ocean.
- 在太平洋的半路上。
I was right.
我猜对了。
He did send himself to Australia.
他确实把自己送到了澳大利亚。
- Crikey.
哎呀。
How many bad things happen to you quads?
你们四胞胎遇到多少倒霉事了？
all: So many.
太多了。
[cheerful music]
[欢快的音乐]
- I can't believe Dicky actually
我真不敢相信迪基居然
shipped himself to Australia.
把自己运到了澳大利亚。
- Maybe he didn't.
也许他没有。
Maybe he just shipped his mobile.
也许他只是把手机寄走了。
- Yeah, he probably packed his phone and clothes
是啊，他可能只是把手机和衣服
in a big box and shipped it to fool us.
在一个大箱子里，然后寄过来愚弄我们。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Box, us, fool...
箱子，我们，愚弄...
- What's happening? - Shh! She's hatching.
- 发生什么事了？ - 嘘！她在孵化。
- [snaps fingers] I got it!
- [打响指] 我明白了！
I think I know a way for us to cut in line
我想我知道一个方法，让我们插队
without Dooley or anyone seeing.
不让杜利或任何人看到。
- Is she gonna tell us what it is, or--
- 她会告诉我们是什么方法吗，还是--
oh, right.
哦，对了。
♪ ♪
- Special deliveray for Get Sportay.
- 特别快递，给Get Sportay。
- What giant thing did you order, Tom?
- 你订了什么大家伙，Tom？
- I order a lot of giant things, Anne.
- 我订了很多大件，Anne。
I don't know.
我不知道。
We're really busy right now.
我们现在真的很忙。
Can you just move it over there, please?
你能把它搬到那边去吗，请？
- Thar? Shar.
- 那边？莎。
[knocks] Seriously? A little help.
[敲门] 认真的吗？来点帮助。
- Okay, we made it past Dooley.
- 好了，我们绕过Dooley了。
- And there's Isaiah Thomas!
- 还有Isaiah Thomas！
- Wait. These aren't my eyeholes.
等等，这些不是我的眼洞。
These are your eyeholes, Nicky.
这些是你的眼洞，尼基。
- Yeah, let's switch eyeholes.
是啊，我们换一下眼洞吧。
[shuffling]
（挪动声）
- Wait. I was wrong. These aren't my eyeholes.
等等，我错了，这些不是我的眼洞。
- Yeah. I want my old eyeholes.
是啊，我想要我原来的眼洞。
- Do I need to tear you both new eyeholes?
我是不是得给你们俩开新的眼洞？
- Okay, everyone, only seven pairs of shoes left!
好了，各位，只剩七双鞋了！
- Did you hear that? Britt, you're up.
你听到了吗？布里特，轮到你了。
- That was weird.
那有点奇怪。
- Do you think they noticed?
- 你觉得他们注意到了吗？
[children arguing]
[孩子们争吵]
- Nope. They're focused on those girls.
- 没有。他们正盯着那些女孩。
- Okay, everybody, only five pairs of shoes left!
- 好了，大家，只剩五双鞋了！
- Yes! - We did it!
- 太好了！ - 我们做到了！
- The shoes are ours! - Ripper!
- 鞋子是我们的了！ - 太棒了！
- So we're not going to get the shoes?
- 所以我们拿不到鞋子了？
- We waited all day.
- 我们等了一整天。
- Look at those sad little faces.
- 看看那些伤心的小脸。
- Guys, these kids are the real liner-uppers.
- 伙计们，这些孩子才是真正的排队者。
- Yeah, we're just liner-cutters.
- 是的，我们只是排队的人。
- Kids! Wow, you made it!
- 孩子们！哇，你们做到了！
- Oh, you guys, I'm so proud of you.
- 哦，你们这些孩子，我真为你们感到骄傲。
You waited in line and you didn't act entitled.
你们排队等待，没有表现出任何特权。
Now you get your shoes.
现在你们可以拿到鞋子了。
- No, Mom. We don't deserve them.
- 不，妈妈。我们不配得到它们。
- We cheated our way up in line.
- 我们用欺骗的方式插队了。
- What? Did we already give Dooley his free pair of shoes?
- 什么？我们是不是已经给了杜利他的免费鞋子？
- Yes. - Dang it.
- 是的。 - 该死。
- These kids have been waiting here all day.
- 这些孩子在这里等了一整天。
They deserve the last pair of Isaiahs.
他们应该得到最后一双Isaiah鞋。
- [sighs] So go on, kids.
去吧，孩子们。
[chuckles]
（轻笑）
Sorry. Guess we didn't learn our lesson about entitlement.
抱歉。看来我们还没学会关于特权的教训。
- I think you just did.
我觉得你刚刚学到了。
- Kids, we're really proud of you.
孩子们，我们真的很为你们骄傲。
In the end, you did the right thing.
最终，你们做了正确的事。
- Hey, that was really nice of you.
嘿，你们真是太好了。
Thanks for giving up your sneakers for my sons.
谢谢你们为了我的儿子们放弃你们的运动鞋。
- Your sons?
你的儿子们？
They why were they standing in line?
那他们为什么还排队呢？
- Well, they didn't want to, but I was teaching them
- 嗯，他们其实不想，但我是在教他们
a lesson about entitlement.
关于特权的课程。
- [gasps] Me too!
- [惊讶] 我也是！
I mean, you know what they say:
我是说，你知道他们怎么说：
"Great dads think alike."
“伟大的父亲想法一致。”
You know, if you want to, uh, hoop it up later,
你知道，如果你想，呃，晚点打篮球，
maybe I can show you a few of my skills.
也许我可以展示你一些我的技巧。
- Oh! - Oh!
- 哦！ - 哦！
- I'm good.
- 我很好。
- Well, I guess we'll have to wait
好吧，我想我们得等到
for the full-priced Isaiahs to come out next month.
下个月全价Isaiah鞋上市了。
- Maybe not.
也许不用。
I was saving a few pairs
我本来留了几双
for my buddies back home,
给我的家乡朋友们，
but since you guys were so nice to my boys,
但既然你们对我儿子们这么好，
I think I should give them to you guys.
我觉得应该给你们。
- Yes! - Please!
太好了！
- Thank you! - Good on ya, mate!
谢谢你！
- Ripper!
好样的，伙计！
♪ ♪
- Those are pretty big on ya, mate.
你穿着有点大，兄弟。
- But they're still awesome.
但依然很酷。
- They were for my teammates, but they can buy their own.
这些是给我队友们的，但他们可以自己买。
Thanks for setting a good example for my boys.
谢谢你给我的孩子们树立了好榜样。
- Anytime, thank you. - Whatever you need.
随时愿意效劳，谢谢。- 有什么需要尽管说。
- Thanks. - Thank you, Mr. Thomas.
谢谢。- 谢谢您，托马斯先生。
- Grab your markers, boys.
孩子们，拿上你们的记号笔。
Last time you left them out,
上次你们把它们放在外面，
I slipped on 'em
我踩到后滑倒了
and couldn't play for two weeks.
并且两周都不能玩。
- I'm in the front!
我在前面！
- Huh. And in the end, it all worked out.
嗯。最终，一切都很顺利。
No wallop. - Wait!
没什么大不了的。 - 等等！
We forgot to get them autographed.
我们忘了让他们签名。
[exciting music]
[激动人心的音乐]
♪ ♪
[slo-mo] - Oh, no!
[慢动作] - 哦，不！
- He's gonna slip!
他要滑倒了！
- I got this!
我搞定这个！
♪ ♪
- I almost slipped on this and sprained my ankle.
我差点在这滑倒，扭伤了脚踝。
Ow, my ankle!
哎哟，我的脚踝！
all: Crikey!
哎呀！
- And there's the wallop.
这就是那一摔。
♪ ♪
- Uh-huh.
嗯哼。
Ooh, uh-huh.
哦，嗯哼。
- Mom, please stop pacing. You're making us nervous.
妈妈，请别再踱步了。你让我们很紧张。
- Okay, all right.
好吧，好吧。
Hey, thanks for letting us know.
嘿，谢谢你告诉我们。
Isaiah is gonna be fine.
以赛亚会没事的。
[all sigh]
（大家都松了口气）
- Well, that is enough excitement for one day.
好吧，今天已经够刺激的了。
- Actually, there's a little more excitement
实际上，还有一点刺激的事情
you need to know about.
你们需要知道。
- Oh, no.
哦，不。
- The boys think Dicky shipped himself to Australia in a box.
男孩们认为迪基把自己装在箱子里寄到澳大利亚去了。
Please tell them how ridiculous that is.
请告诉他们这有多荒谬。
- Well, Dicky is in Australia.
嗯，迪基确实在澳大利亚。
- We shipped him there. all: In a box?
- 我们把他送过去了。大家: 在一个箱子里？
- No. - No, on a plane.
- 不是。 - 不是，是坐飞机。
We shipped his clothes in a box.
我们把他的衣服放在一个箱子里寄过去了。
- Yeah, we told you all this this morning.
- 是的，我们今早已经告诉过你们了。
- Oh, hey, kids.
- 哦，嘿，孩子们。
Early bird gets the shoes, huh?
早起的鸟儿有鞋穿，是吧？
- [yawns] We were just at the airport.
- [打哈欠] 我们刚从机场回来。
Dicky got picked at the last minute to go to Australia
Dicky 在最后一刻被选中去澳大利亚
as a part of the student exchange program.
作为学生交换项目的一部分。
[both yawning]
[两人都在打哈欠]
- He was so excited to see
- 他看到反向冲水的马桶时兴奋极了，
a backwards toilet flush,
我们立刻把他送上了下一班飞机。
we put him on the next flight out.
- 我从未见过他们这么乖。
- I've never seen them so well-behaved.
我们确定是他们吗？ - 当然。
Are we sure that's them? - Of course.
- 哦，是的。 - 完全记得。
- Oh, yeah. - Totally remember.
- 我们可不傻。
- We're no dummies.
[手机响了]
[phone chimes]
- 哦，快看！Dicky刚发了条短信。
- Oh, check it out! Dicky just texted.
上面写着：“看这个超棒的！”
It says, "Watch this awesomeness!"
[toilet flushing]
Huh. It really does go backwards!
哈，真的反着冲水！
all: Ripper!
所有人：太厉害了！
[toilet flushing]
- What's that?
- 那是什么？
all: Ew, crikey!
所有人：哎呀，天哪！
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪